<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <data>
        <variable
            name="id"
            type="java.lang.Integer" />
    </data>
    <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:orientation="vertical">
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="comment"/>
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="@{id.toString()}"/>
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. This is very long text you won't believe. "/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>
</layout>